http://www.mexinsure.com/legal/privacy

Quote/Purchase
Automobile – RV – Motorcycle
Driver’s License Liability Insurance Policy
Northbound Insurance (Seguro Auto USA)
Driver’s License Liability Insurance Policy
Northbound Insurance (Seguro Auto USA)
Privacy Policy
Here at Mexico Insurance Services we do our best to proactively protect your data. There is no completely secure system but we employ the latest technologies and techniques to ensure your data security. We use SSL on the web forms to ensure the transmission tunnel is encrypted and we use Paypal (formerly Verisign)'s 128-bit encrypted payment gateway. This means we don't even store your credit card information locally, that they are housed and encrypted at a world-class facility far out of reach of hackers.
We created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to the privacy concerns of users of our website and to disclose our information gathering and dissemination practices. Except for the purposes set forth herein, Mexico Insurance Services will never sell or transfer your personal information to any unaffiliated person for any reason. "Affiliated person" may include, but is not limited to, third parties that have been retained to aid with customer service, help with hardware/software maintenance and upgrades, and/or our foreign insurance/roadside assistance providers.
Personal and Non-Personal Information
Cookies
Internet Protocol (IP) Address
Clickstream
Consent to Processing
Other Sites
Additional Information
Choice Opt-In / Opt-Out
Personal and Non-Personal Information
When using our website, you may be asked to provide certain personal information about yourself for the purposes of purchasing, sending or redeeming a gift certificate, entering a contest, responding to a survey, etc. In general, Mexico Insurance Services will only use this information to comply with the purpose for which such information was requested. Mexico Insurance Services may, from time to time, use this information to send you information about new and exciting products and services offered by Mexico Insurance Services. Mexico Insurance Services will not share with or rent, sell or lease your personal information to any unaffiliated person or entity without your express consent. At any time you may revoke this consent by contacting us at the address provided below. We may also request and collect non-personally identifiable information about you, such as gender, age, hobbies, or buying preferences. We may use this data to improve our site and to send you information that may be of interest to you. We may use this data to enhance your experience at our site, showing you content and promotional messages that we think you might be interested in, based on your preferences. We may also share this information with others, such as advertisers interested in advertising on the Mexico Insurance Services Web site, in aggregate, anonymous form, which means that the information will not contain any personally identifiable information about you or any other person.
Back to Top
Cookies
"Cookies" are pieces of information that are placed on an individual's computer hard drive to enable the individual to more easily communicate and interact with Web sites. Mexico Insurance Services may use cookies to customize your experience on the Mexico Insurance Services Web site. We may use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, save your password (if you have registered with us) so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, and for other purposes. You may, however, disallow receiving cookies at any time through your web browser. Mexico Insurance Services will never use cookies to retrieve information from a computer that is unrelated to the Mexico Insurance Services web site or your interaction with the Mexico Insurance Services Web site.
Back to Top
Internet Protocol (IP) Address
We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you for the duration of a session and to gather broad demographic information.
Back to Top
Clickstream
As you browse the Internet, a trail of electronic information is left at each Web site you visit. This information, which is sometimes called "clickstream" data, can be collected and stored by a Web site's server. Clickstream data can tell us the type of computer and browsing software you use, the address of the Web site from which you linked to the Mexico Insurance Services Web site, and in some instances, your e-mail address. We may use clickstream data to determine how much time visitors spend on each page of our site and how they navigate throughout the Mexico Insurance Services site. We will only use this information to improve the Mexico Insurance Services Web site. Any collection or use of clickstream data will be anonymous and aggregate, and will not contain any personal information.
Back to Top
Consent to Processing
By providing any personal information to this site, users, including without limitation users in the European Union, fully understand and unambiguously consent to the collection and processing of such information in the United States.
Back to Top
Other Sites
Our site contains links to other sites. Other sites may also reference or link to our site. Mexico Insurance Services is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other sites.
Back to Top
Additional Information
If you want more information about our Privacy Policy feel free to write us at service@mexinsurance.com.
Back to Top
Choice Opt-In / Opt-Out
If we ever send you information by e-mail concerning new Mexico Insurance Services products or services, we will provide you with an e-mail address by which you may request no future notices. If you have already consented to receive such notices or have your information shared with unaffiliated parties, and want to rescind this consent, send an e-mail to service@mexinsurance.com.
Back to Top
×
Account Login
Username
Password
I forgot my password
×
Account Register
Please visit the Kelly Blue Book website and enter in your vehicle's details to find the most accurate value for your vehicle.
×
Group Code
If you belong to a group or special affiliation, and know the code, enter it here.
